♪ In the not-too-distant
future ♪
♪ next sunday a.d. ♪
♪ There was a guy named joel ♪
♪ not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ he worked
at gizmonic institute ♪
♪ just another
face in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ he did a good job cleaning
up the place ♪
♪ but his bosses didn't like him
so they shot him into space ♪
♪ we'll send
him cheesy movies ♪
♪ the worst we can find
(La-la-la) ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ and we'll monitor his mind
(La-la-la) ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
joel can't control ♪
♪ where the movies
begin or end
(La-la-la) ♪
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ to make his robot friends ♪
♪ robot roll call
cambot ♪
♪ gypsy
hi girl ♪
♪ tom servo!
What a cool guy ♪
♪ crow!
He's a wisecracker ♪
♪ if you're wondering
how he eats and breathes ♪
♪ and other science facts
(La la la) ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ for mystery science theater
3000 ♪♪
[Gates closing]
Oh...
Got five seconds to live.
Must get personal finances
in order.
Joel, joel,
thank heaven you made it.
But what the heck was
that thing?
We lost tom, buddy.
Oh, I hate to think of him in
there with that, that...
Wait a minute,
I'm blind, I'm blind.
That thing cut me.
[Tom]
Crow, something is wrong on
saturn three, oh!
[Crow]
Looks like I got it, man.
At least I found joel.
Panty-weight passed out in all
the excitement.
[Tom]
Keep telling
yourself that, crow.
Oh, what do you mean, tom,
you're crying?
We're all together again.
- Crow!
- I was just with him!
Don't you do it,
don't you dare you do it.
[Tom]
Joel, joel robinson
is dead!
Oh, god, he's dead.
- Hey, just kidding.
- Whoo-hoo-hoo.
Hey, you look great.
♪♪
[All laughing]
Oh, we do have fun,
don't we?
But what was
that line again, crow?
Oh, you mean, "I'm blind,
that thing cut me."
No, no, no, no, that other one,
that... don't you--
oh, yeah, oh, yeah.
Don't you do it!
[All laughing]
Oh, just a second,
the mads are calling.
Don't you ever let me catch you
fooling around like that up--
well, if I was up there right
now, I'd spank your hinder.
Well, let's just rage on with
the invention exchange, frank.
Tall and proud.
Okay, my name is bond,
frank bond.
Right, and I'm ursula andress.
I know.
Do I have to do everything
around here, frank?
Oh, sorry, boss, it's just that
when you're a top secret agent
with a license to kill
like myself,
you always find
yourself in scuba gear.
But not only that,
there's that endless series
of formal parties,
dances
and dinners
that you have to attend.
I mean, it's really easy to fit
a tuxedo under a wet suit,
but what about footwear?
Show the product,
frank.
Smile.
Introducing the formal flipper.
Step out of the ocean
and into high society
with the formal flipper.
By bass,
and what about the ladies?
The ladies,
uh, pan down,
jerry.
Hello, federal.
Oh, could we just
get on with
your invention exchange
you blinking
pinky ring?
I want children.
You know, joel, every day
in every way
those guys are
getting weirder and weirder.
I know, I couldn't agree
with you more.
Anyway, my invention exchange
today is based on the premise
that kids just don't like
to wear hats in the wintertime.
You know, I mean,
hats smash your hair down.
Headbands make your hair
all staticky
and earmuffs
just plain look dorky.
You know, I remember winter,
sledding down the back hill,
over the creek,
under the old bridge,
past the sullivan's big
dark trouser,
waving to lois
and sabrina.
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Anyway, anyway, you two.
This is a new invention
that will allow kids
to look cool and stay warm
and avoid all that
peer mockery
that we all know
can harm us
well into adulthood.
Check it out.
They're earmuffs
that look like ears,
see what I mean.
Okay, here, put them on,
let's see how they look, yeah.
Okay?
Hey, I feel like
prince charles.
Yeah.
And they'll come in a rainbow
of colors eventually
to match everybody's
countenance,
okay, look.
Oh, so suddenly
I look like
jimmy j.J. Walker.
Right, and they'll also
come in
a lot of novelty styles, too.
Like for next year's big
sci-fi leviathon in,
um...
In anchorage, alaska,
I've invented these:
Vulcan earmuffs.
- Ah.
- See?
Fascinating.
Live long and prosper.
Not!
Ahh!
Oh, so joel--
we don't see you wearing
any of these dopey earmuffs.
Yeah, what's the deal?
Oh, well, you guys,
looks are deceiving.
You see,
not only am I
president of ear club for men,
- I'm also a customer.
- Wow.
What do you think, sirs?
Very nice, sy sperling.
Tell 'em about the experiment
this week, frank.
This week's experiment
is called
jack, mighty jack.
It's produced
by frank,
sandy frank.
Oh, push the button,
send 'em the movie, frank.
I gotta get out of these
size nines.
- [Alert buzzing]
- What, what?
Oh, we got movie sign,
whoa!
[Gates opening]
Those guys are-- oh.
Hey, "mighty jack".
The story of a brave pancake
starring aunt jemima
and flap, the wonder dog.
Mighty jack, the dog--
isn't that a dog food?
- Could be.
- I don't know.
Good idea.
Featuring our
all vegetarian dishes.
"Hitaki, teriyaki,
and naoko koko... kobo."
Ah, they should really
waterproof
this basement.
George...
Marsha.
Cornjob.
Kind of soap
opera music here.
♪ I am a lineman ♪
♪ for the star fleet ♪
Yee-hoo.
Love bug 2000
starring
admiral gavin macleod.
Say...
[Mimicking trotting horse]
Writers,
oh brother,
tell me about it.
[Mimicking trotting horse]
Now there's
jessie "the body" vogel.
[Chuckling]
- Mayor.
- He's right.
[Mimicking trotting horse]
Yee-hoo.
I'm not too proud of this,
just print my name small.
I don't blame him.
♪♪
Ooh, dramatic.
Sex cameraman,
is this--
- no, no, s-f-x, joel.
- Aah.
Hey, twin evinrudes,
yeah, but you know,
I got a bass boat flyer
up on the front there.
You got one of them
big bass chairs up front?
Oh, you bet'cha.
Gotta keep your tips up
when you're getting pulled
behind one of them babies.
[Together]
Mighty jack!
Hm, whoa.
Come on.
We don't
need to see this.
No, no, no.
Declaring that
if they continue to fight
among themselves they face
an even greater danger
- from an unexpected source.
- Peggy lee.
An organization,
known as "q", equipped...
Whoa, we're falling off
don't do that.
...more than ever
to pursue its goal
of complete conquest
of the earth.
To carry on
its diabolical schemes...
[Joel groaning]
Help him.
That funk & wagnalls
is heavy.
Among friendly
peace-loving countries...
Let's see, "p"...
Kitty!
Can no longer stand by
silently and tolerate...
Japanese calvin and hobbes.
Therefore, the president
proposes to form
a team of specially
trained men and women
to combat the organization
known as q and stop...
Cue for the narrator.
This team will be
code named mighty jack.
Using the latest technology,
mighty jack will have
as its mission
the annihilation of the
organization known as q.
[Snoring]
But it will not be an
easy task.
For q is clever...
[Loud snoring]
- Start!
- Cue that up!
[Chuckling]
Live from
the q-note cafe,
the q-tips.
[Jazz playing]
Tokyo, 10:00 a.m.
Do you know
where your children are?
Saigon, 7:30 a.m.
Hey, he's eating
q-rations.
Hmmm.
Moscow,
it's 7:00 a.m.
And paris, 2:00 a.m.
Ah, paris, city of lamps.
Hey, look, richard carpenter's
getting drunk.
Unbelievable and karen.
- Come on, finish it.
- Finish it, whoo!
Hey, geraldine ferraro.
Oh.
Who's the guy?
[Whispering]
Girl.
Hey, it's jfk.
Wow.
Bobby.
Okay, let's see now.
Why do bees
suddenly reappear...
Oh, screw it, forget it.
Monsieur?
Won't you stay with
me a few more minutes?
While I spackle my teeth?
Hey, django reinhardt.
- Nah, too many fingers.
- Oh, you're right.
A japanese in paris.
[Mimicking japanese accent to
"an american in paris" theme"
[chuckling]
Was that kind of racist?
No, no,
I don't think so.
- Door is ajar.
- Ding-dong.
- Ignite cigarette.
Have second thoughts
about girl in bar.
Ding-dong.
[Chuckles]
Hey.
♪♪
[With french accent]
Oh, lord, won't you buy
me a mercedes benz.
My friends
all drive porches...
Ah, we're coming to the fork
in the plot.
- Don't take a wrong turn.
- What?
Well, it's kind of a keith
haring painting it looks like.
Huh?
Whoa!
[Tires screech]
Oton, ichton,
schlotomeyer.
Shh, ixnay, french.
Oh, bonjour.
Huh?
Shield your eyes
from the net!
Ooh, big, big.
It's the helicopter
from "daktari."
Oh, they're gonna return
that japanese car to the wild.
- Oh.
- They gotta tag it.
Bon voyage!
You will always
have "paree!"
- Oh, boy.
- [Horn honking]
You can always tell
it's a japanese net,
it's filled with dolphins.
Oh, what a burn.
[Man]
Just relax, mr. Atari,
and enjoy the ride,
- it's a beautiful night.
- For a moondance.
Look, what do you
think you're doing?
[Man]
Your altitude is 2,000 feet.
I'm sure you'll enjoy
the view,
good night.
To your left you'll see
the champs-élysées
and the rive gauche.
This is no place
for a convertible.
John wayne is brannigan.
Medical center
in color.
Ooh-hoo,
that's good weed.
Hmm-mmm.
Hey, it's j. Edgar hoover.
I will crush
the kennedys.
Come in.
It's regarding
mr. Atari, colonel.
I've made several calls
to paris to try to get more
detailed information.
On the day he disappeared,
mr. Atari left the cabaret
at 2:00 in the morning.
Drove past
the port dordogne
heading south.
And then he suddenly disappeared
along the highway somewhere.
And the airports?
- Nothing as yet.
- [Snickering]
[Snickering continues]
All right, that'll be all,
thank you.
Oh, god.
[Sniffing]
I am so high.
[Thinking]
It's not a case
of robbery.
I'd better
contact mighty jack.
Why is my internal voice
different from external voice?
Inside I'm tan
and handsome.
Outside, I'm the grinch
who stole christmas.
[Dialing rotary phone]
[Kissing sounds]
Hello?
Hello, is that you,
catherine?
Hey, what are
they opening a boutique?
She'll not have my apple.
It's mine.
Here's the message
from colonel yabuki.
My bookie?
I want you to rescue
a certain man.
He disappeared
suddenly near paris.
He's very important
to mighty jack.
It could be a dangerous
mission so be careful.
Oh, and sabrina,
you pose as a scientist
and wear that string
bikini we got you.
That's the man.
Say, that's a man?
Oh.
How interesting.
Oh... you know a lot of
girls that look like that?
This one I do.
- She's a well-known dancer.
- Cool.
She's not missing,
it's the man we're looking for.
Oh, too bad.
So he's our next
assignment.
Measure it.
His name
is harold atari.
He's a professional
mountaineer.
♪♪
What about that transmitter?
I kind of looks like
the $10,000 pyramid here.
What's being done
to find it?
Captain tenda and lieutenant
jerry are out searching
with the electro scout.
Ah, things you
say in a dolly shot.
Well, the maximum range
is 700 miles.
Uh, things
you'd say to marconi.
There shouldn't be any problem
if it's within that radius.
Things you
keep in your purse.
Hmm.
There's one slight
problem, though.
Uh, things you
say when you're dim.
Mr. Atari doesn't know he has
the transmitter on him.
Then he won't
know that we...
You see, catherine,
I had it issued
merely as a precaution that...
Things you say in a teacup.
... mr. Atari was called away
very suddenly,
before he was
instructed in its uses.
If he doesn't find
it, then.
- Sooner or later...
- Love is going to get you.
... he will discover
that he has it on him.
Bless us, our buddha, these--
wait, I'm not a buddhist.
You're shinto.
Wait a minute.
Button, button,
I've got the button.
And I'm gonna use
it, too.
Hmm, the button's
kind of dull.
Hmm, like this movie?
[Chuckling]
Woo!
Haza, alakazam,
and I'm gone.
Oh, I gotta
work on that.
Got the patter down,
though.
If I'm not mistaken
I should have a rabbit
over there at least.
Oh?
[Gasping]
I was just
daydreaming, doctor.
God.
Very well,
and when are you coming back?
I'm not sure.
Don't stay away
too long.
If you
know what I mean.
You've always been
one of our best men.
- Thank you, sir.
- I think.
Oh, do you
see that box there?
That suit, it's my parting
gift to you.
From spiegel,
chicago, illinois, 60609.
Wait a minute,
is this a flashback.
I-i-I'm lost.
Hmm, good workmanship--
morty must've made this.
Nice hankey poof, too.
Hmm,
what a weird guy,
he gives lovely parting gifts
after a meeting but i--
hm?
You hear anything?
No, I've got wood clamps
on my ears.
It's no use.
I'm not
getting a signal.
I'm going to try
further west.
Crest, crest.
[Mimicking flatulence]
Ha-ha,
I love that one.
[Imitating mr. Rogers]
Hi, boys and girls,
I'm gonna take my shoes off
and put my little
sneakers on.
[Sniffing]
[All gagging]
Oh, man,
you need dr. Scholls.
It either smells like bad meat
or good cheese, ooh!
Phew!
If I'm not mistaken,
there's a phone--
uh, oh-no,
that's just my insole.
Oh, I see,
there's a hee--
a really good hee--
what?
Oh, wow, cherry cordials,
what a thoughtful
old man.
See.
Oh, playing
house is fun.
Table for two, sir?
Oh, oui, oui.
I'm having a tea party
for my little friends.
Ooh.
Coats a real rip-off.
Wouldn't you say that?
Let's see, uh, paperclip,
and old stick of gum... uh.
See what else I got in here.
A bunch of peanut shells from
that karaoke bar stuck in there.
For crying out loud.
Well,
he's building a meal.
You see, he's got the four
button groups, check 'em out.
[Humming]
I did it one piece at a time
and it didn't cost me a dime.
[Humming]
Oh, great, the instructions
are in japanese.
D'oh!
[Humming]
♪ People come from trees ♪
[Chuckling]
It's a one-hitter.
What's he doing there?
That really held his
tie in place, didn't it?
Maybe he can get into the craft
fair next year with that.
[Beeping]
They might
be monitoring it.
They might be
giants.
[Beeping]
- There it is again.
- [Beeping]
This is only a test,
had this been
an actual movie...
It's gone again.
There's one thing
pretty sure, though.
That was on
the 20-meter band.
- Booty's 20-meter band?
- Rubber.
It's much too far
to figure out, sir.
Try to get the general
direction.
- Uh, that way?
- Pacific ocean.
A specific ocean?
Yeah, but which one, be more
"pacific," ha-ha!
- Jerry, look.
- Jerry?
Dean, we're flying in
the thing with...
[Imitating jerry lewis]
Oh, look.
That must be a wedding,
they're throwing rice.
Really big rice.
They're holding hands
and skimming stone.
Toy boat.
[All]
Toy boat, toy boat,
toy boat.
Toy boat.
Oh, it's the captain
of the valdez, there.
Hm, stately, plump buck mulligan
came down from the stairwell--
this book is awful.
No pictures.
[Man]
Doctor!
I got this
awful headache.
Okay, climb in.
Looks like
you're homesick again.
No, no, it's not
that at all.
It's those
crazy radio signals.
They get louder and softer
and softer and louder.
They're driving
me out of my mind.
[Chuckling]
But I'm getting a lot
of interference.
They're transmitting
about every ten minutes.
Butyl nitrate?
Uh, something suspicious,
though.
There's no station
on the 20-meter band.
It's a calamity.
You say it's
on the 20-meter band?
Yeah.
Maybe that's atari.
Try to get the exact direction
of those signals.
Do it immediately.
Couldn't you give me some
medicine first, doctor?
I'd prescribe me,
dr. Jack feelgood.
Meanwhile, back
on the greasy bastard.
When did you start
hearing them?
When I was ten.
I picked up the first
signals a few days ago.
I was trying to get headquarters
but reception was bad
so I changed
wavebands and noticed it.
Now I'm getting the rush
limbaugh show.
Oh, doctor, that's it.
See if you can get
the exact location.
Yes, sir.
Enough of these damn
bureaucrats in washington
spending all our hard-earned
dollars in lazy welfare slums.
Back in a moment.
This is my last chance,
I must risk it.
[Tone signaling]
This is lay canon with
the jazz image, tonight.
- [Tom imitating bass line]
- That's the signal.
It's very close,
it's him all right.
- Him?
- It's atari.
Stop them transmitting
those signals.
Isn't that
right, flopsy?
- [Gasps]
- Huh?
[Gasps]
Oh, no.
Oh, no, it's the shower massage
by waterpik.
- Are the signals gone?
- Yes, sir.
Only they lasted over
five minutes this time.
Wow.
Good, did you get
the location?
Yes, 7-0-7-0.
[All]
Sunset strip.
Okay.
- I can't do that.
- You get an "a".
[Chuckles]
Dr. Hyde heard signals
on our emergency band.
He's either keith richards
or he's dead.
I can't quite tell.
The frequency's the same as on
mr. Atari's transmitter.
Does anyone
know what's going on?
Anyone?
Lime-green, orange-orange.
There's no
island in that area.
It could be a ship.
They say the transmitter
was stationary.
Well, they say that
falling in love is wonderful.
Then it must be an island.
Well, then, we'd better
send out mighty jack.
Hmm, he lives in a drawer?
Oh, yea-- no.
Unzip me, would ya?
We'll link up
with mighty jack soon.
Yes, sir.
What a wild sensation
that'll be.
Whoo.
Hmm.
Ah, this must be the symbolic,
cinematic love scene.
Ooh.
[Humming]
All right,
full speed ahead.
- Elvis costello.
- Oh, cool.
Course southwest.
- Decorate in pink and blue.
- We must be careful.
That man
stole their hostage.
Hmm, nice.
Aw, now he's gotta
watch hazel,
- strapped in the
eric roberts sex chair.
- Mr. Atari.
What do you want?
[Man]
I want you to tell
us about your mission.
Never.
Then tell us
about the rabbits, george.
[Man]
As long as you cooperate,
no harm will come to you.
Well, I'd call that harm.
Ooh.
[Man]
Those lights are
capable of blinding you.
I'm not afraid,
I'll keep my eyes closed
but I won't answer any
questions.
Wow, is he smart.
[Man]
You're being very foolish.
Soon, you'll open your eyes and
then you'll be blinded for life.
Tell us one thing.
Where is
comedy central?
Where's mighty jack's
secret base?
I don't know.
Hey, he's getting
tan and handsome in there.
I don't know anything.
Atari, you mustn't underestimate
the strength of q.
Our agents
are everywhere.
Paris, berlin, london,
madrid.
- Fresno.
- Why did they send you
to paris?
'Cause I loves paris in
the springtime, that's why.
I was there to meet a business
colleague of mine.
We sell amway.
- And then I did
a little sightseeing.
- Hmm.
It is no use stalling.
I promise we'll
let you go.
But first, you have to tell
us everything we want to know.
But no slides.
[Man]
You can't hold out
much longer.
I'll ask you once again.
Where is mighty
jack's base?
It's next to the drums
and the guitar, ha-ha.
I've never heard of
mighty jack.
[Man]
What a stubborn man you are.
I hope your eyes
are still closed.
Now for the last time,
where is mighty jack's base?
It's not easy being green.
I'll tell you
what you want to know.
Just turn off the lights,
please.
[Gates closing]
Okay, uh, everybody,
you know what to do?
- Servo?
- Roger.
- Uh, gypsy
- richard.
Uh, yeah, whatever.
Okay, places everybody,
he's coming.
Hey, hi, you guys,
what you up to?
Well, you know, we've been
talking about how humans
have a need for pets.
Like in this film,
the evil guy has a pet cat.
Yeah, and humans have a lot of
programming and commercials
directed specifically
at pets so...
So we've come up with a little
ad campaign based on this movie.
Yeah, and we'd like you
to be our test market.
We'd like your feedback,
you being human and all.
- Pretty much, right?
- [Gypsy] Come on, you guys,
[gypsy]
I got stuff to do.
Okay, well, I'd love to see
what you guys got going,
- what you got cooking.
- Okay, give me a second.
Okay, here we go.
Uh, cambot,
hit that music.
♪♪
New from the makers of
mighty dog and hungry jack
comes a taste combination
that can't be beat.
Introducing mighty jack!
Hi, I'm mighty jack.
I make my
own gravy, ha!
Joel, give me a hand,
pour that water on me.
There you go, whee,
hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo, ah-ha.
Mighty jack dog food is high in
protein, low in sodium,
pure beef, partially
hydrogenated, great tasting feed
made with a mature member
of your family and mine.
That's some
mature dog, I mean...
Ahh!
Mighty jack has
the taste dogs love
and is completely free of
perfumes or stabilizers.
Strong enough for a manx
but made for a rottweiler.
Store in a cool, dry place and
do not expose to living tissue
or temperatures
over 72 degrees fahrenheit.
Now available in three
delicious flavors,
regular, mailman and cat.
I'm so hungry
I could eat a horse.
I have just one message
for all dogs.
- Bite me.
- Hey!
Ahh, I'm being eaten
by a dog, help me out!
Remember,
mighty jack dog food
and the mighty jack
corporate symbol
are in no way representational
or meant to infer
relationship to
any similarity of any other
corporate symbols, logos or
trademarks, dog foods,
dog treats, dog snacks
or persons living or dead.
- The end, what do you think?
- What do you think?
Uh, I think we have very
different views of advertising.
Let's see how
the pros do it.
♪♪
I will, master.
- I'll take care of colonel...
- My sweet lipstick.
- Ah, hey.
- Secret agent estée lauder.
In easy spirit pumps.
- Well...
- You'll be...
And you'll be hot,
hot, hot
with the latest talking
lipstick fashions from paris.
Breath of fresh air, ha!
I'll fix her real good,
you can bet on that.
Don't forget,
I'm counting on you
to accompany me to
the meeting tonight.
What about my needs?
I'll send the car
for you.
- Okay.
- Come in.
She's a lousy traitor,
sir.
Hey, it's
the doublemint geishas.
If that's all,
I'll go home now and prepare
for tonight's meeting.
- And for being a traitor.
- Bye.
Here's the receipt
for your depends.
Hmm, let's see,
"bite me," what's this mean?
♪♪
Hm?
[Sniffing]
Do you...?
Wait, this mirror makes
me look like a modigliani.
This is really
a wonderful painting.
She has such
mysterious eyes.
Actually, it's my father.
Ooh.
- They're contacts.
- Wow.
I've always
enjoyed modern art.
Not!
I know it sounds strange...
But I
think I'm a zebra.
We don't know very
much ourselves.
All they told us
was that the kidnapped man
was very important
to mighty jack.
Ash, please.
There's one thing
we do know, though.
Ash.
The kidnappers must be
clever and ruthless.
We can't just sit
here like this.
We're getting hemorrhoids.
Mary, have they
found the site yet?
Unh-unh, I'm waiting for
their next message, though.
- Nice flip.
- Oh, no, time for band
practice.
- ♪ Well I used to get-- ♪
- hi, elvis!
I don't know
how important he is
but he's sure giving us
a lot of trouble.
No trouble at all.
- This is a joy ride.
- Huh?
When he finds out that mighty
jack's on the way to rescue him,
he'll jump for joy.
[All laughing]
A signal.
[Beeping]
♪ Western union ♪
♪ dah dah-dah dah-dah,
dah dah-dah dah-dah ♪
Calling mighty jack,
calling mighty jack.
Come in, mighty jack,
respond immediately.
This is mighty jack.
We have a nuclear missile
aimed directly at you.
But we have no
intention of attacking you.
We only demand that you
turn over mighty jack to us,
in exchange for
mr. Harold atari's life.
The anti-missles are loaded,
sir, ready to fire.
Shh, not here.
We have already delivered
this demand to colonel yabuki.
Do you read me,
mighty jack?
How do we know that
mr. Atari is still alive?
Wait a moment.
- Are you alive?
- Exchanging him for
mighty jack.
Who is
this atari anyway?
Captain tenda?
All we know is that
it's someone very special.
Hello, mighty jack,
it's me, harold atari.
Mr. Atari, mighty jack
will rescue you.
You'd better rescue me.
I don't feel like
being left out here to rot.
Why of all the--
say, who does he think
he is?
And be quick about it.
Unless you're
all frightened pigeons.
Boy, that's the last straw.
Pigeon, yourself.
Hey, watch your mouth.
If you don't think
you can handle the job,
you might as well turn
around and go home.
- Ooh...
- Listen to that.
- What a burn.
- Well, I've had enough.
All right, let's go home.
Why should we save him?
Look, heckling is
part of the business.
- I admire his courage.
- You would, kiss-up.
Do you read me, mighty jack?
Well, what
have you decided?
Hmm?
We read you all right?
We need a little time.
Very well, we'll take
this up with colonel yabuki.
[All]
♪ yabuki, yabuki, yabuki ♪
Is everything
ready for the conference?
- Helen of troy.
- What's the matter?
I'm through making
coffee!
[Gasping]
You've finally
revealed your true colors.
You're the one who
betrayed us.
I'm disappointed in you.
Accept the proposal
they've offered you.
Atari's life in exchange
for mighty jack.
It's pure beef.
Unless, colonel,
you would rather exchange
your life for mighty jack.
[Laughing]
Oh, gramps, get some
pearl drops.
[Gasping]
Huh?
Oh.
All right, drop the gun.
I'll just place it very
carefully on the counter and--
[shouting]
[Laughing]
She won't get very far
in those cheap pumps.
Feel like
a sneaker, though.
- Sam spade's office.
- Hmm?
Spacious.
- Mcgarrett, get her!
- Mannix, stop her!
Hooker's a good cop.
I gotta say it.
Ooh.
Sorry I blew up
like that.
- Hm, so?
- She's dead, sir.
I believe she had swallowed
some sort of lethal capsule.
And then it--
wriggled and wiggled
and triggered inside her.
It exploded inside her.
As if it had been triggered
off by remote control.
[Tom and crow]
The crappy game show?
Okay, kids,
come on, it's in or out.
Close the screen door,
come on.
Ooh, whoa, it looks
like it's getting kind of
low on baking soda.
Yeah, that happens.
Come back as soon as
you've scouted the island.
Gotta get this suit back
to ivan tors.
- Roger.
- Whittaker.
[Chuckles]
[Jazz playing]
Wow, it's the island
of miles davis, cool.
You know, I bet he has a
perfectly dry tuxedo under that.
Or a perfectly dry martini.
Glenn corbett,
what are you doing here?
Huh?
♪♪
Oh, it's
aaron spelling's house.
Oh.
Ikiba.
[Grunting]
You know, I've always
wanted to see the inside
of bebe rebozo's house.
[Tom imitating nixon]
Dick.
Powder blue,
spies ask for it by name.
[Whispering]
Cool, daddy.
♪♪
Something tells me
that wynton marsalis
is around
the next corner.
Oh, akio, akio,
wherefore art thou, akio.
♪♪
Whoa, big dog,
rottweiler, ooh.
Ooh, look out.
[Gasps]
That's teo macero.
♪♪
Calling mighty jack,
it's jerry.
Mighty jack,
I see you finally made it.
Hey.
Where's the installation?
On the south side
of the island.
How's atari?
Kind of a jerk
but he grows on you.
[Chuckling]
And so the male zygote swims
out to meet the egg and--
♪ hey aqualung ♪
"Navy seals"
starring charlie sheen.
Uh...
Hello, mighty jack.
I'm on
the island now.
I'm gonna try
to recue them.
Yes, sir.
Uh, I'll just cover
my scat here.
Now let's see
what we have here.
Uh, chicken leg.
Oh, kraft singles and a note
from my mother:
"I'm so proud of you."
What is that,
a pool cue or a silencer?
Just put that part on,
that makes it loud again.
Oh, and that attachment for
the hard-to-reach assignations.
[Chuckles]
How many
silencers does he need?
I don't know.
Boy, you know,
these fern prisons
WERE REALLY POPULAR
IN THE '70s, WEREN'T THEY?
Natch.
Puma?
- Todd?
- Watch out for that palm leaf!
♪ Dum, dum, dum, dum,
dum-dum, dum ♪
I will succeed
where he failed.
Jerry, where are you?
Oh, hello, mr. Rescue person,
I'm in the...
It's the door
on the right.
Okay.
It's by
the ice machine.
I have a feeling that
kooky chaos is about to ensue.
It's the m.C. Escher house.
Escher house.
[Singing]
Oh.
Room service.
Is that you captain,
the door's locked.
Oh, thanks
for knocking, dean.
They're trying to kill us
with poison gas.
Who, exxon?
Oh, boy.
Oh, that'll help a lot.
Hold still.
It's better
if you don't move.
We've got to get
out of here.
I saved my handkerchief.
[Coughing]
It's here
in my espadrilles.
It's a snap.
Come on.
[Panting]
Wait.
Before we go.
We have to
blow the place up.
Oh, that's craz-- why didn't
you tell us that before?
- Okay, let's do it.
- Let's fall in love.
Jerry, return to mighty jack.
- What about you?
- I've got the buggy here.
- But, captain.
- That's an order.
Yes, sir.
He never lets
me drive the buggy.
Don't move!
You moved... ooh.
Hey, give me a turn
at that.
Ooh, it's fun.
- All right, let's go.
- Right.
[Exploding]
Yeah.
Unreal.
Ooh.
Pretty.
They sound like horses,
don't they?
What?
What, we got a volkswagen?
What-- oh, great,
good thing there happened
to be a chopper around.
[Chuckling]
Traffic over the
pacific ocean is light today.
Expect no delays between
mindanao and hawaii.
Looks like the ty-d-bol
man traded up here.
The water's blue.
Yeah.
We're informal here at
mighty jack, steve.
Shirtsleeves.
Wow.
Well, then,
down the hatch.
Orrin hatch, you see that's
a little joke
for our friends
in utah, senator.
Fine, distinguished
colleague from...
All right, engines on.
- Yes, sir.
- Combat stations.
Boy, just think if this
movie had a plot.
It might really be neat.
Yeah.
Huh?
Neat decals.
- Yeah, nice.
- Excellent detailing.
Wait a minute.
Sherwood schwartz presents
gilligan's island 2000,
with gilligan,
♪ the admiral too ♪
♪ the billionaire ♪
Weenie launch, weenie launch.
Wow.
No!
Oh, no, they hit
the howell's hut.
Lovey, I'm on fire.
Flash.
[All]
Ohh...flash.
It gets
tiring after a while.
Hoo, "apocalypse now,"
ah-ha, apocalypse not.
December 7, 2041,
a film
that will live in infamy.
Oh, look, the mosquito.
The minnesota state bird--
for our friends in minnesota.
Weenie launch.
Test.
Ooh, ooh!
[All]
Aahh...
[Clapping]
Oh, beautiful.
It's memphis belle.
Ooh, ooh, ooh, oh, oh,
wow, oh.
Beautiful.
They're using every toy
in the box.
Here comes
the grand finale.
More thrust.
Really?
Gamera!-- uh--
oh, sorry.
From the fun and sun capital of
the world, miami beach, comes...
Oh.
You know,
the tommy bartlett show
is really getting expensive.
Now we see here where
the patriot missiles
intercept the scuds.
And...
God bless
the patriot missiles.
And we'd like to welcome you
to collateral damage playhouse.
Wow.
Whoo.
- Did you do that?
- Let's go after them?
It's no use.
Their speed is
much faster than ours.
I can't believe it--
faster than mighty jack?
Never underrate
your enemy.
Uh, I think
that's how it goes.
Anyway, we saved mr. Atari
and that's all that matters.
[Man]
Captain.
I think we ought to destroy
the island completely.
Okay, mr. Manifest destiny.
Tommy, let's go
back to the island.
Yes, sir.
Bank turn.
Accidents will-- huh?
I don't like that guy--
who does he think he is?
Careful, he might hear you,
he's a v.I.P.
Yeah, you don't say.
We risk our necks to save his
life and now he's giving orders.
Hey, nice hat.
We'll be over
the target very soon.
Say, captain, should we
drop a few bombs?
It'll keep him
quiet for a while.
Good idea.
That's what
kissinger would do.
Hey, that's a baby
formula factory.
Now you've done it.
Ah, tet, my
favorite holiday, you know?
There goes the ken and
barbie dream home.
Ooh.
Oh, no, not the
a.m. radio towers.
Clark and hanson in
the morning...
God, I love
the smell of burning flesh
and the sound of
breaking glass.
Ooh.
Well, then.
Mission accomplished.
Now let's go home.
The wimbledon
judges agree.
[Chuckling]
- Dickweed.
- Ooh.
Tag.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, boy, here
comes another...
[Together]
Bank turn.
How many more you
gotta look at?
[Man]
You have not
destroyed us, mighty jack.
We will retaliate
for this.
Our organization
is powerful.
Q will return and
annihilate you forever!
But first these messages
from crest.
Yeah, yeah, we all live in a
yellow submarine, we know, yeah.
Superslow...
Moving car.
Super slow.
Da-dum.
Meanwhile, at the movie's
biggest phallic symbol...
Hey, pull my finger.
Oh, jeannie's really done it
this time, major healey.
I'm going out,
anybody need anything?
We finally made it back
to base.
And we're not
allowed to get off.
Those were the orders
from headquarters.
Poor guy.
[Singing]
Oh-ho, the chicks are here.
Whoo!
Welcome back, jerry, the mission
was successful, wasn't it?
Yeah, but
I didn't enjoy it.
Oh, and that's all
that matters.
Why not?
Well, you see,
uh, there was this guy.
I just couldn't
stand him.
Ooh.
Doh!
Ask not what your country
can do for you.
[Gasping]
Allow me to introduce...
Major harold atari.
[Together]
♪ wha, wha, wha, wha ♪
Open mouth,
insert foot.
Heh-heh-heh.
Haikiba.
Welcome aboard...
Commander.
The captain is
your executive officer.
He'll be kissing up to
you right away.
Captain?
It's an honor, sir.
You got a cute smile.
Lieutenant jerry.
No, with the thing--
I'm sorry, the, no...
It's good to see you.
I'd like to thank you
for rescuing me.
Oh, it was nothing...
If you hadn't come.
- Sir, allow me to introduce...
- We should get going.
Our other crew members.
- Come on...
- I don't know.
With its new commander,
the mighty jack team
is complete.
♪♪
Guys, hey guys, what's--
hey! No! I knew you
were gonna do this to me.
Would you get this thing
off my head?
Silence fool, silence!
- Meow.
- Thank you, there,
there flopsy.
You'd better tell me
what we want to know.
The lights in there are capable
of blinding you.
[Joel]
Oh, that doesn't bother me.
I'll just keep my eyes shut.
D'oh, foiled again
but boy is he smart.
You can say that--
would you knock it off.
- You're supposed to be a cat.
- Uh, meow.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, sure.
Hey, would you guys hurry up,
it's hot in here.
Joel, aren't you just
the tiniest bit curious
about those blinding lights?
Don't you want to
peek just a little bit?
No!
Hey, like I said,
he's smart.
Oh, boy, guess all of those
swimsuit posters on the wall
are going to go completely
to waste, aren't they?
And I guess you
wouldn't even be interested
in that rare paul klee
painting on the wall, either?
Oh, you guys don't have
a paul klee painting.
- Boy, is he smart.
- Yeah, the guy is smart.
Aren't you
supposed to be my cat?
- Um, meow.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- Oh, I got an idea.
Joel, I seem to have misplaced
the hope diamond.
Would you look
around in there for me?
- Oh, it's not in here.
- Well, did you even look?
No, I'm not going to.
- Boy, is he smart.
- Smart is the word.
[Together]
Plan b, plan b, plan b.
Okay, joel,
I hate to get tough,
but inside that box with you
is a poison "samich."
Uh, I just won't eat it.
D'oh, foiled again.
You've completely lost
the cat thing, haven't you?
I admit it,
I'm way off script.
I've got no
idea what I'm doing.
- Oh, guys, come on.
- What're you...
It's so uncomfortable
in there.
Oh, has the great
joel robinson decided
that fun time is
over now?
Cheesh.
- Man, what's the matter with--
- okay, joel, don't say hi.
- Meow.
- You have got to be
kidding me, crow!
Hey crow, you wanna go get some
frozen yogurt or something--
[gates opening]
[Buzzing]
Hey, we got a movie...
Oh, my cigarettes
are ringing.
You think
you're so smart.
- Meow.
- Shut up.
Atari, here.
[Man]
We have problems.
What?
They've destroyed
the installation.
We'll have to
recarpet everything.
Yes, I'm afraid so.
It's q again.
Nothing compares to q.
We urgently
need the titanium alloy
for a top priority military
research project.
Got any in
your junk drawer?
How soon can you be ready
for redeployment?
Well, let's see, I have to
shave and then I'll want to eat
a decent breakfast with toast,
scrambled eggs and black coffee.
That's fascinating,
get over here!
Take your time.
Ha, ha.
And don't forget,
I want scrambled eggs...
- D'oh!
- It really gets me off.
[All]
♪ wha, wah, wah, wah ♪
I'll have
some orange juice.
Yes, sir.
And don't
forget the toast.
Oh, that razzy son
of a gun.
- Engines on.
Then strap your
hands across my engines.
- Toast is ready, sir.
- Ready for submerging.
- Submerge!
- Submerge.
I said, dry toast.
How are we on
the about-this-big meter?
[Man]
Water level, 50 feet.
- Unlock gates.
Daryl gates, david gates
and bread.
There's
the toast thing again.
What's with the toast?
Why'd they fly through
the window?
We've replaced the pacific ocean
with folgers crystals.
Let's watch.
We'll first search
the area in the arctic zone.
- Yes, sir.
- Open the venetian blinds.
On course, sir.
What's our present
speed?
Mach two.
I've got a mac classic.
Maintain speed and proceed in
the direction north-northwest.
See if
james mason's there.
North by northwest,
that's kind of a stretch.
Enough with
the bank turns.
Really.
♪ You ain't woman enough
to take my mighty jack ♪
Yee-who.
Wow, it's
the cover of "dianetics."
And another bank turn,
thank you very much.
They're chasing that bright,
elusive butterfly of love.
Kyle maclachlan.
You know it's
really good today, isn't it?
Um-hmm.
They're all enjoying it.
Sir, what's that?!
Ha! Made you look.
Oh, that's
just the set of "orca."
Oh, it's just an iceberg.
We'll be at the north pole
in five minutes.
Heh-heh.
Santa claus
going to be there?
Hey, it's ice station
zebra.
And look, howard hughes
is in his drawstring shorts
and he's got a mason
jar filled--
oh!
[Menacing laughing]
Neat.
[Gasps]
Evil good humor men.
Enemy approaching.
Prepare to
launch missiles, pronto.
Oh, he's italian.
How about allegro.
The enemy
has now gone.
Close missile sites.
Meow.
Freezer
door won't close.
They really should defrost.
That was q all right.
A clever hiding place.
Until spring hits.
We'll just wait
till we're ready to attack.
What a blowhard.
Our first duty is to go inspect
the frozen island.
And then figure out why
the howells had so much luggage.
Oh-- hmm?
I'm batman.
Now, see, that boat must
have very low fat content.
- Now why do you say that?
- Going right to the bottom.
Holding position.
There's no trace of the station
at the bottom of the sea.
Maybe they
succeeded in floating it.
- How's the goatee coming?
- They could have removed
it in separate sections.
Yes, though I don't think
they had time to dismantle it.
- Eddie, yuri.
- Yes, sir?
Put on your diving suits
and scout the whole area.
Yes, sir.
You, put on your diving suit
and meet me in my cabin.
- Yes, sir.
- Keep radio contact.
Yes, sir.
Somebody else,
say, "yes, sir."
- Yes, sir.
- Thank you.
[Together]
Toy diver,
toy diver, toy driver.
It's toy donahue.
[Chuckles]
It's a toy dive--
ha, ha...
Sorry.
Flipper is made
of liquid metal.
♪♪
Oh, wow, man, they're
swimming right through
robert schuller's
crystal cathedral.
Look, sir!
Oh.
Load the rockets.
Wow, jet-propelled
blue gills,
I read about it
in "field and stream."
Fire!
Yes, sir.
[Torpedos roaring]
Uh-oh.
Look out.
A direct hit.
With a bullet going right to
the top of the charts.
- Jerry, reload rockets.
- Yes, sir.
- Mary, keep tracking them.
- Barry, you grab mary.
- Yes, sir.
I think one
of them's hurt.
When models goose themselves,
next on geraldo.
- Laser gun.
Laser gun
starring pat carroll.
Uh, could someone explain to me
what's going on here, please?
- It makes no sense.
- Absurd.
Eddie, yuri,
are you all right?
Answer.
Please phrase in the form
of a question, sir.
We're going
after them, get ready.
Yes, sir.
- Mary, radio headquarters.
- Yes, sir.
Doctor hyde,
you take over.
- Yes, sir.
- It's mister hyde, sir,
ha-ha-ha.
Hmm.
[Mimicking underwater talking]
Oh, wow, look, it's a way cool
kind of scary jell-o thing.
What was the research
agency's conclusion?
I don't know,
they haven't announced it yet.
It's imelda marcos.
There's one thing
that bothers me, sir.
My sergeant pepper outfit.
There was a strange cargo ship
in the harbor.
I had the feeling that it was
spying on our installations.
I tried to
get its nationality,
but then it vanished,
suddenly.
Wow.
Would you
recognize it again?
- Yes, I'm pretty sure.
- Could you pick it out
of a lineup?
Well, then I think you
ought to do a little
sightseeing along the docks.
- Yes, sir.
- Say.
[Sexy]
- Yes, sir.
Here is that report
from the technical
research agency.
Oh, hey, look, it's
the old druggy guy again.
They believe the island
had no density.
It was only h2o.
That means no massive land,
merely solidified water.
[All]
You mean, ice?
Then it should be
floating on the surface
because of the specific
gravity.
Could you
be more specific?
I can't believe it could sink
to the bottom of the ocean
without melting
in the warm water.
It's against all
the laws of physics.
Can we make it stick,
can the d.a. make a case?
One thing is certain,
to melt the ice,
they require intense heat.
Or there's
another possibility.
Q has found a way to convert
molecular energy.
- Those stinkers.
- D'oh.
Various scientists
have been working on it,
but q may have found
the solution.
- Q's on first.
- That's what I'm asking.
Third base.
If such an important
scientific discovery
were used only
to serve evil purposes.
Q is powerful.
They may have been able
to infiltrate our
own research center...
Duck.
Or maybe they have been
able to bribe some of
the scientists working for them.
- Goose!
- Nice counter-blocking, dad.
Well, principally
dr. Takebana of japan.
I think the cameraman's
kind of lost interest
in what's going on there.
Dr. Takebana is...
Wallpaper theater will
be back right after this.
[Woman]
Could they have some
connection with q?
Could they be agents
for the organization?
They're talking about us.
I love when
they talk about us.
[Man]
...To investigate
the matter for us.
But they finally reported...
Now that is a swell
blaupunkt.
In-dash reel-to-reel.
Have you got
their photographs?
Got any wallets?
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
That's charles durning
and walt disney.
Uh, what?
Oh, cherry car, man,
glass packs and thrush pipes.
Oh, man.
Look at this.
This is cnn.
Huh, planned parenthood?
Stop the kettle drum.
Meow.
[Man]
Come in, gentlemen,
come in.
We are now entering the final
phase of our operation.
The time has come for us to use
all the means at our disposal.
Even you,
the ritz brothers.
And especially mighty jack.
They have annoyed us
too long.
I wish you every success
in this our last combat.
Good luck, gentlemen.
Now, you may go.
- Yes, master.
- Yes, master
[menacing laughing]
Hmm, why didn't they call me
master?
Ooh.
On the waterfront.
Oh, wow, she's got no toes,
foot binding.
[Horn blowing]
What is she, a merchant marine
all of a sudden?
Aqua marine,
that's the color.
Oh, my aching
imperialist dogs.
[Humming]
[Gasping]
[Gasps]
All right, lady, which detergent
do you prefer?
Haikiba!
Whoa.
She is a lean, mean,
lime green
fightin' machine here.
[Grunting]
Good job.
Oh, wait, wait, wait,
two on one?
Hey, hey, come on.
Oh.
Uncalled for.
Hold it, right there.
Ricky ricardo!
Oh, ricky,
they're beating me up
for messing up
in the chocolate factory.
[Grunting]
Ooh.
Come with me.
♪♪
Hey, she's been kidnapped
by the partridge family.
And they're playing
"echo valley 6080209".
♪♪
[Gasps]
♪ Cuando para mundo ♪
♪ condido escobar ♪
♪ esta mi corazon ♪
♪ chi chi chimichanga ♪
Oh?
You're back with us again.
Where am I?
Vaser requisiton.
My name is bobby zimmerman.
Cozy, isn't it?
Have you any idea
of what they wanted?
No, I had no idea at all.
Maybe they were
after my money.
Thank you for rescuing me.
Nothing,
don't even mention it.
Okay.
- Oh.
- Something annoying you?
Yeah, your capo.
You're manuel perez.
No, I'm sancho panza.
I recognize you.
Aren't you manuel perez?
[French accent]
Oui, I am that person.
You've always been
a hero figure to me.
I've read your books
and know all about
your early struggles.
Say.
You did such good work
in the third world.
Oh, are you speaking to me?
Are you still involved
in politics?
♪♪
Whoa,
the politics of motion.
The politics of feeling good.
Ah, we'll order off the menu.
Oh, man, look at
the appendix scar,
who's the body double,
jack klugman?
Yeow.
Uh, we're trying
to eat over here.
I love going to friday's.
Salut.
I was in anna christie
at the provincetown--
thank you.
[Jazz playing]
Excuse me a second.
- Look after him.
- Sure.
She's going to throw up.
What took you so long?
I was beginning
to get worried.
- Was that the ship?
- No.
But something else happened.
Q tried to kidnap me.
[Gasping]
Only I was saved
by this man, perez.
Did he give you those jammies?
Hey, a view master.
And it's mount rushmore.
Hmm?
- It's mel torme.
- It's don adams.
- Noel coward?
- Tommy sledge?
Oh, can I help you?
Are you looking for
anything special.
Well, no,
I'm just browsing around.
You see, I have to do
a lot of traveling
so I'm always
buying travel guides.
That's a picture of you naked.
You are sick.
Special correspondent
for world magazine.
Roberto okumura.
Well... you're the famous
writer, aren't you?
Well, could be, your guess
is as good as mine.
I read one of your articles
a short while ago.
It sucked.
And I thought you did a
wonderful job describing
q's increasing power
in the various countries.
Oui, I did do that.
I see you have a rather
special interest in it.
Mighty jack interests you, too,
I guess.
What, no, we're just having
some coffee...
I don't know what you mean.
I'm only a salesgirl
in the store here.
I got another tip
for mighty jack.
Why don't we step out and have
a little cup of coffee.
Just the two of us.
Building castles
in the sand.
We can chat about mighty jack.
It's got a lot of friends
in this store.
- Roberto.
- Hmm?
I don't think that your readers
would be interested
in what goes on
around here, do you?
Ah, you're the person in charge
here, mr. Atari, right?
Still trying
to watch pong, eh?
Yes, the famous mr. Atari.
[Chuckling]
You know what puzzles me?
The newspapers often
talk about mighty jack,
but nobody does
anything about it.
They never mention the crew,
not once.
Only the mechanical details.
The design and all its
latest equipment.
I have a responsibility
to our readers.
I'd like to write
about who the crew is.
All the human interest stuff,
you know.
Well, then write
what you have to.
Uh-oh.
[Screaming]
Oh, I forgot it's
tuesday!
Are you all right, roberto?
No, my elbow exploded,
what do you think?
Oh, oswald.
No, no, no.
Hey, don't point,
that's not polite.
But wait,
mr. Ice cream man.
Up there, the roof!
Up yours, you goof!
Kato, look out!
Blasted.
Darn dern-ma-gergot.
- Jerry!
- Where is he?
He got away.
Oh, what have you got there?
Waith, wait,
he's talking to himself.
I found this
on the staircase.
Your windsong
stays on my mind.
A strange looking bullet.
It's transparent.
Like this plot.
I've never seen anything
like this before.
- How did it go?
- Same results as before.
Is that so?
We raised the heat to 800
degrees without melting it,
or even altering
its molecular structure.
It's definite proof that--
shh!
The man might be listening.
Ha!
Oh.
Ah.
Rolling papers,
I'll roll us a doob.
You put on some
allman brothers.
That "eat a peach" album.
[Chuckling]
[Gurgling]
I hear it's a wonderful
afternoon to be doing...
You knew about that?
Sometimes it's necessary to keep
the enemy well informed.
I thought that we ought to tell
them we knew
about the high temperature ice.
Now we'll wait and see
how they react.
Oh.
You mean, roberto?
Durán?
Yes, he's an agent of q.
And perez?
Well,
we'll always have perez.
There's no proof yet.
Catherine's investigating
that now.
I understand dr. Takebana
will be returning tomorrow.
Good,
we'll go question him.
Is the doctor a q agent?
[Mocking]
- A job for you, atari.
- Yes.
On a very special
"trapper john, md."
Oh, it's thirsty thursday.
Two bucks for a mug and then
raspberry cosmos
are a buck after that.
- Interesting lecture.
- I'm glad you enjoyed it.
I did some research...
Excuse me, doctor,
we'd like to speak to you.
- Not now, I'm very busy.
- It's about hot ice.
[Gasping]
Wow, my favorite band.
Here.
It's not made of glass,
but only of water.
But it's the best I can do.
I believe you were working on
this experiment.
Uh, did you clean
that off real good?
Ooh.
Ice, ice, baby?
Would you gentlemen excuse me?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
About a thing...
Thank you.
Oh, fritz, I'll take that.
Fritz.
Sure think, stotch.
We, uh...
This is fritz,
he's my assistant.
- Atari.
- How do you do.
[Clearing throat]
How do you do.
Well, I must go now.
Goodbye.
- Shall we go to my office?
- All right.
♪♪
Someone broke in
and stole all my records.
- Jim nabors, ed ames...
- Ten years of research.
I'd nearly completed
all my experiments.
And then one day,
all my papers were gone.
So I quit my route.
What a tragedy.
Liberté, égalité.
And now I see that someone
has carried my work
to its final stage.
Ice that won't melt even under
very high temperatures.
[All]
So what?
Sheesh.
Atari, have you any idea
who could have stolen them?
Could it be dr. Von muller
from west germany?
Wrong, go fish.
He's engaged
in similar research
though our methods
are quite different.
If you analyze
this substance,
you will see that it
could not have been made
without using my process.
Which is liquid metal.
Could it have been fritz,
your assistant?
- No, definitely not.
- Why not?
You see,
fritz is my son.
You named your son, fritz?
And my wife died
many years ago.
She was german.
- So you're available.
- Fritz is my son.
He grew up in berlin.
I understand.
Atari, I told you
a little while ago
all that work of ten years
had been stolen.
I lied.
It was a great loss.
But now I realize I was wrong to
speak about my work prematurely.
Oops.
It was out of vanity.
And apollonia.
♪♪
What do you think?
Let's go italian today.
It's hard to say if he's
telling the truth.
But he sounded very sincere.
There's still one suspect.
Who?
Dr. Von muller.
Oh, the chinese guy.
Let's go then.
Mystery guest,
sign in, please!
Well, here we are at dr. Klutzy
von doorknobs place.
Well, atari,
it's good you're here.
I'd like to introduce this
gentleman to you.
This is dr. Von muller.
We've been smoking
lebanese blonde
and we're flying right now.
- How do you do?
- Doctor.
[Mimicking buzzer]
- Joy buzzer.
- Love that gag.
Please sit down.
- Atari?
- Sir.
- Where do you get
your suit waxed?
- Dr. Von muller also claims
that all his research and
documents
have been stolen.
Oh, andy, oh...
My research documents...
Yeah, it's true, yeah.
Then you're half japanese,
half french
with some vietnamese mixed in,
is that right?
Yeah,
they call me mongrel boy.
During the war,
I was sent to school in italy.
316 speed, that's all
I ever heard.
My parents thought I'd be more
sheltered there.
I never saw
either of them again.
They both died in vietnam.
Oh, that war.
[Whispering]
Shh, don't talk about that war.
I'm sure you suffered
a great deal then.
Suffered, oh, yes, yes.
But today the world's a
different place.
There's so much to live for.
Oh, you don't know
the half of it, hm.
They say...
That the happiest people
are the ones with faith.
What are you barbra streisand
all of a sudden?
Oh...
I'm afraid that
I left my cigarette lighter
in your store the other day.
[Chuckling]
The one who stole those papers
must be working for q.
We have to try and set some kind
of trap to discover the traitor.
- Right-- harry, eddie?
- Yes, sir?
Find out who else
had access to those files.
Hey, what's william faulkner
doing in there?
Did you see a lighter?
Hey, that scene just hooked up
with the other scene.
- Wow, now they're back-- oh.
- Here it is.
Thank you.
And here's something for you.
Oh.
Well,
it's been real nice.
See you later, kid.
♪ Ooh-bee-doo-bee-doo ♪
♪ bah-dah-dub-dah ♪
♪ bah-bah-bah-boom ♪
Ah, rupert murdoch.
[Whistling la marseillaise]
Enough.
Now we have to pay
the french government.
Oh, this is just like
the chase scene
from "the french connection."
So that was french,
the whole french thing.
It's very french.
Oh, they're just going
to spend some time
in the discipline box, there.
Mighty jack.
Perez... avanti.
Si.
Si?
Been waiting long?
All my life.
Ah!
That long, huh?
I'm going out to eat now.
I just came into
a little money.
Are you free for dinner
tonight?
Yes, I am.
Arby's okay?
Is this your car?
No, I borrowed it
from a friend.
Oh, I see.
I know a terrific new place.
Come on, get in, okay?
Do you understand him?
Unh-unh.
Um, take me
to the nearest plot point.
Nice helmet, there.
♪♪
Say, you're kinky.
So anyway, that's why
I use old spice.
Ahh.
Enter.
Enter, whatever happened
to come in?
Sorry, dear, I'm afraid
we have to put you in steerage.
Please.
Tight, that captain.
Ha, ha, arrr.
Pronto, pronto.
Pups, mini-doughnuts,
cotton candy,
that sort of thing.
[Speaking italian]
Ooh-ee-ooh-ah-ah.
Ting-tang-walla-walla-bing-bang.
What khadafi's hosting
science theater?
Operation two, completed.
Get on with this.
- [Speaking italian]
Bene, pronto.
I'm off script now.
[Chuckling]
What did you say?
I don't know,
it was italian.
I think I ordered wine.
In amori bay,
they're now constructing...
- Amori?
- ... a new island
for their experiments
to replace the old one.
But I just gave orders
to have it destroyed
with our iceberg method.
- Iceberg menace?
- Destroy it?
Of course.
Once it is destroyed
you will no longer be able
to develop the weapons
to defeat us.
Q will then be the most powerful
organization in the world.
The whole of the united nations
will have to submit to our will.
You filthy traitor.
Thank you,
say that again.
You're not going
to get away with it, though.
Mighty jack will stop you.
Yeah, whatever.
So you admit
there's a connection
between mighty jack
and you.
- She sang like a bird!
- D'oh.
No matter what they try,
mighty jack is now powerless.
[Gasping]
No...
Nothing will help them.
Oh, why do you say that?
'Cause it's my line.
[Menacing laughing]
You're stuck here.
Perez, contact our agent
right away.
Get us out of this film.
Um-hmm.
It's woody guthrie.
Hey, my mood ring's
going all kooky.
Hmm?
Adam west?
Pete dupont?
That looks like pete.
Hello, father.
Hello, mother.
Uh, here I am in okinawa.
So you were the one.
Yes.
You should have realized
it long ago.
I opened your safe and gave all
your records to q.
- How could you?
- No.
All my life's work.
You of all people,
my own son.
Yes, I knew you'd say that.
All my life, you could only
think of me as japanese.
But inside I'm german.
Kind of
like sushi stroganoff.
How much did they give
you to betray me
and work
with those monsters?
You've never acknowledged...
Now he looks like roddy
mcdowall.
I don't get it.
All those years,
you took the credit.
Only now things will be
different.
I'll have
my own laboratory.
With q I have a
great future.
My own room and
my own phone, too.
Your future for stealing
another man's ideas.
Ooh.
Betraying your father
by dealing with murderers?
- Yes.
Your ideas and ethics
are too antiquated
for you to understand
what we are creating.
Look at my warts,
I have to be evil.
We will
conquer the whole world.
Well, it's good
to have goals.
Fritz.
The wicker man?
Now they're in ireland.
Why did we come here?
I have proof that dr. Takebana
was working for q.
[Gasping]
I'm going to check out his
apartment.
You stay as lookout.
Can I go with you?
You stay here.
Oh, no!
We can't stay here,
we gotta go.
We go.
You stay here,
we'll go.
Come along.
[Gates closing]
Help, help,
crow's flooded the ship!
We're all gonna die!
A fire ball!
Joel, come on, you're not
fooling anybody.
That's an aquarium we put in
front of cambot
that's causing
this effect here.
I know, I know, I was just
getting ready
to do a big pitch
to hollywood.
You know, we got tons of offers
from interested executives
after crow read his piece in
reader's theater
called "earth versus soup."
Yup, uh, now I've got a
development deal
with anson williams
enchantment productions.
And plus, I'm doing a rewrite
on "next of kin two."
Yeah, so I thought we could do
the pitch underwater, you know.
Like cash in on some of the
excitement that's been generated
from movies like "the deep" and
"the abyss" and others.
Wow, that's a
great idea, joel.
As a matter of fact, I was just
watching "mighty jack,"
and I couldn't help but think
this would make a great movie.
Right, yeah, okay.
I was thinking
something like start it off
with a submarine,
like:
[Mimicking sonar ping]
Gray lady, down!
I can't see 'em, they got a
caterpillar here, sir.
Nice, joel, that's nice.
Ha-ha, great, joel.
The man should be in a
straitjacket.
Noah's floating.
Here come the animals,
two by two.
Whoa, what does noah have to do
with anything here, joel?
It's the
ark of the story.
That's it, that's it.
Go tear his arm off.
Hey, wait a minute,
what are you trying to do?
Uh, I was gonna tear
your arm off.
Oh, come on.
Anyway, the really good thing is
that steven spielberg
is now doing a bunch of movies
based on cartoon characters.
You know, like "the flintstones"
and "bloom county."
And, uh...
Just goes on like that.
Yeah, what's he
gonna do next?
Casper, the friendly ghost?
Oh, that'd be ridiculous.
You know,
and I was thinking
it'd be a great
time to bring
even more cartoon characters to
the big screen, you know.
- Like, deputy dog.
- That's droopy.
And, uh, odie colognie.
And josie and the pussycats.
I can't stand to see him
like this, crow.
No, I can't either.
Hey, you guys, come back.
I can be nutty just like
the rest of you
and do dumb puns
and stuff like that.
There's no reason
why I can't.
I'm-- you know, I'm weird and
that results in creativity.
Well, speaking of
the nutty,
here's a word from our friends
at shake-a-pudding.
♪♪
I thought it was a pretty good
idea, actually.
Oh, it's sinatra, he's going
right for the scotch.
Yeah, wouldn't you know it.
She's got judy carne hair,
there.
Mary?
- Tyler?
- Moore?
All right in the box?
It's okay.
Oh, it's a rock tumbler.
This should pad out
the film a little.
- Oh, no.
- Yep.
A nice little toy.
A portable synchroton unit.
Oh, you made that up.
Dr. Takebana changes water
to ice instantly
by accelerating
their molecules.
You accelerate my
molecules, doctor.
Anyone has the power to alter
molecular structure anywhere.
And they usually do.
And you can even make ice
bullets?
Yes.
Oh.
[Laughing]
You think that's funny?
It's fritz.
You can tell by his blinking
pinky ring.
Hmm.
Oh!
- Ooh.
- Ouch.
Takedown, two points.
[Grunting]
Oh, look at that reversal,
another two points.
You two want some gum?
It's a lady sunbeam.
[Beeping]
That's mary's signal.
Just what I've been
waiting for.
What do you mean?
I assumed q was
clever enough
to detect
if anyone was acting.
- Oh, no danger of that.
- Mary doesn't know who
their agent is.
Oh, you like
living dangerously?
- Let's go, doctor.
- Let's play doctor.
[Chuckling]
Anytime daddy-o.
[Tom imitating music]
See if you can get rush
limbaugh.
Yeah, that's him.
Can't get rid of it.
Get rid of it, dear god,
it's on every station!
Get rid of it!
Whoa.
We're on the wrong
side of the street.
- Major, I'm so glad to see you.
- It's japan.
- Where'd they go?
I'm not sure about
dr. Takebana.
Roberto tried to stop
fritz but he got away.
He made off with the
portable synchroton.
Synchrotron?
- Yes.
- Sounds like a soap opera.
[Phone ringing]
Folks, it's just a phone.
- Ooh.
- Pick it up.
Hey, come on, it's my
dad from florida.
Shut up, sven, come on!
- Be cool.
- Dr. Fritz?
Ja.
We'll go ahead as planned.
The ship is waiting at the
shubaro maru dock.
The sheep? There's a sheep
waiting for them?
Ja.
Ja, jawohl, mein kampf,
all that stuff.
Q must be trying to help
dr. Takebana
and his son escape.
Is that part of the plot?
Better call for a backup.
Yes, sir.
[Humming]
The man that we're
waiting for.
We're just
waiting for a table.
Well...
So just plumb ran out of things
to say here, huh?
Senorita,
you're coming with us.
He asked me, he asked me,
today my dreams come true.
And make sure that dr. Takebana
doesn't commit suicide.
Yeah, he's always pulling that.
Papa.
Oh, good, a familiar face,
adam west is back.
Don't go away,
I'll come right back.
Please, don't you
try anything.
Don't touch that dial.
♪♪
Oh.
- [Tires skidding]
- [Crow making engine noises]
Oh, it's like "what's up, doc"
all of a sudden.
Come on, punch it, hal,
I wanna die with you.
Oh, chinese fire drill.
You mean japanese...
Oh, right, right.
Oh, they're gonna make balloons.
The ship's down there.
You cover the other side.
- I'll cover the waterfront.
- [Humming]
[Alarm sounding]
Who's whooping?
Just another few minutes.
I'm sure fritz will show up.
Yes.
Roberto...
Clemente.
It's strange you only
mention fritz.
You should've said dr.
takebana and fritz.
Ooh!
It's not true.
All right, mr. Q.
I think you better
start talking.
I was born in the house my
father built.
If dr. Takebana
isn't a q agent,
why did you lead us out
here like this?
Uh-oh.
Look!
- No, you don't!
- I don't believe
- he fell for that.
- Unbelievable.
He was only stalling us to give
them time to get away.
He'll kill catherine.
[Gunfire]
They hate these cans!
Hell, these ludlum
novels are-- huh?
All right, get inside,
come on.
Mighty jack.
Mighty jack!
The door will only open for
11 pre-registered voices.
"Ocean's eleven."
I'm not one of them.
Bring her here.
Oh.
Try swordfish.
Well, then...
I'm going to change
your spark plugs.
That will make her talk.
I don't think shooting me is
going to help.
You are right.
But now we'll get a chance to
see how good this gadget is.
We're going to make
monster bubbles.
Gee, no, oh!
Major nelson snowed on her.
There you see, it flocks evenly
with no mess.
Have a christmas tree,
this'll do the trick.
♪ Dah-dah-dum ♪
Robert ludlum will be back in
the uvula scenario.
Don't shoot her.
It's no use, we're lost.
Q is too strong.
There's nothing we can do to
stop them.
[Menacing chuckle]
Go on!
Oh, fitting room number
four is open, sir.
Hey, there's a rule, one
person per fitting room.
This is quite an
installation here.
Yes, rick, it is.
[Gunfire]
Uh, give me a sandwich,
would you?
Would you get to the pier?
Yes, sir.
No, I'll go instead.
- Hurry!
- Yeah, ham on rye
and take off the anise seeds,
I hate those, okay? Thanks.
- [Water splashing]
- Oh, she's going to
the aqua deli.
Scarf theater will be back
right after this.
Okay.
It's the righteous brothers.
- ♪ You've lost that... ♪
- ♪ synchrocylotron ♪
Oh, got a bad clam, huh?
[Muffled groaning]
Oh, not that old gag.
Come on.
Move.
- Go on.
- No tricks.
[Grunting]
Ooh, samsonite luggage.
Let's get out of here.
Wait.
- Hmm? What?
- Okay.
Oh, the plot was moving a little
too fast for his liking.
♪♪
Well, then.
It's a pineapple roaster.
Watch us roast your pineapple
slice, you pick it.
Pineapple roaster?
I love it.
That's funny, you
gotta admit,
roasted pineapple
slices, it's neat.
Okay, come.
Hold it.
Now hold it up to
the lights.
Oh, that's better, we're in a
completely different film now.
[Humming]
And we call it the
postage meter.
We will surprise
them, come on.
- Having fun?
- Surprise!
[Laughing]
Now!
[Gunfire]
Ah, we shouldn't have taken
the time to laugh.
This thing is great.
Ooh.
William faulkner grabs
the package.
Ooh.
Darn.
You, stunt left,
you, slant deep.
You, write "sound
and the fury."
Let's go.
Yeah, you got holes
in your gun!
Yeah, well, you got peanut
butter in my chocolate.
Yeah, but t-- hmm?
[Water running]
- Pew pew.
- Drop it!
[All]
Da-doh, da-doh.
- Come on.
- I'm shot.
Come on, come on.
Ooh.
All right, now, you, slow dance
and don't try to lead.
- I got a gun.
- [Joel laughs]
It's the yancy street gang.
Hasta la vista, baby.
I may be german but I'm fast.
[Laughing]
Don't move!
Oh, no way out.
[All]
Hey, fritz... oh, come on,
what--
[explosion]
- Ooh!
- No.
- Boy.
- Fritz.
He died as he lived.
Loving his work.
♪♪
It's disneyland tokyo.
- Ah, here we are at
plot recovery.
- [Joel imitating ventilator]
- All right.
- [Ventilator noises continue]
Everybody get in the shot,
come on, stay on camera.
How are you?
A little weak.
Q is going to...
- What about q?
- Yes?
They're going to destroy the
island in amori bay.
With the freezing process?
Yes.
I overheard roberto
give the order.
It was for today.
- You must hurry, sir.
- Don't touch me.
Let go of me.
You must hurry.
You must sink the bismarck.
Get back to mighty jack,
full scale alert.
- Yes, sir.
- Combat stations.
Yes, sir.
♪♪
Again with the bank turn.
For crying out loud.
Increase speed.
But I'll get car sick.
Nuclear rockets.
Ready to fire.
Engine room.
Gauge indicates
temperature's rising.
- Pineapple's up.
- Hmm?
Frost 'em.
Make 'em icy.
Oh, master, ready to engage
mighty jack.
Am I still in this film?
[Crow meows]
At last.
Coolant not reacting,
temperature rising.
- Mojo rising.
- Increase speed.
The iceberg,
q's headquarters.
Major, let's hit
them right now.
We'll never have a
better chance than this.
Yeah.
- Get ready to fire.
- Right.
[Whistling sound]
Huh?
Uh-oh.
Fries are up.
What is it, what's wrong?
The a's are much
too high, sir.
200, sir, the temperature is
continually rising.
Another 100 degrees
and the engine room
will explode.
What are we gonna do?
Well, don't go in
the engine room.
We gotta find a way to
reduce the temperature.
Jerry, see if dr. Takebana
can help us, go on.
Yes, sir.
Um.
[Alarm sounding]
Jerry!
They'd better hurry or q will
blast us right out of here.
They're working on the
synchroton now.
They bought that
synchotron thing.
High school shop classes are
quickly taken.
Can't you hurry?
They're helpless out there.
I'm doing all I can.
Try that switch.
You try it, I'm bitter.
I'll take over.
Try the backup system.
Yes, sir.
You guys had all semester to
work on this.
Jerry, jerry, how's it going?
The temperature's still rising,
I can't seem to control it.
Ooh.
Hurry, doctor, you've gotta
get it working.
Um, um...
Sir, the temperature
is still rising.
We'll explode any second,
what shall we do?
I can't change the laws of
physics, captain.
I've got to have 30 minutes.
I've got it,
it's working now.
It's working.
He just plugged it in.
It's working, it's working.
Direct it onto the engines.
And get a little on
the plot if you can.
Right there.
You die, bazooka joe.
All right, now, fire.
Oh, yeah.
[Tom breathing heavily]
Oh, it's good for me,
how about you?
The ice is melting.
The temperature's dropping,
the temperature's dropping!
Great.
The a's are down but you can
never count 'em out.
You know with those a's...
All systems functioning.
Start up.
Shut up.
[Crow laughs]
All right, let's get them.
Continuous bank
turn continuing, sir.
[Laughing]
All right, enough of
that shot, too.
It's balsa wood.
I think so.
They always whistle
under water,
they are under
water, aren't they?
I don't know but
it's really dark.
[Tom humming]
Oh, they bent the ship.
Hey, go down to ben franklin and
pick up another one, would you?
[Tom humming]
Here comes super car.
[All]
Super car.
Look, new underwear,
fruit of the loom.
[Crow making car noises]
It's gamera.
Oh.
It's the bubble and
flow version.
[Laughs]
Laser gun.
Launch rockets.
Bland movie.
Ooh.
You know, this really isn't a
very good movie.
- No, it's not.
- Second battery.
Fire, second battery.
Fire screenwriter.
♪ We have to sink the bismarck
we had to do the job ♪
Hey, johnny, quit
splashing in the tub.
Ooh.
Third battery!
What's-- did he say
turd battery?
- Hmm.
- Attack.
What do you think they've been
doing, come on.
Defrost.
Ooh!
Oh, they hit the
cherry center.
Doggone it, that about
does it, doesn't it?
- Yes.
- They stopped firing.
We got them.
We shot them.
And the fries are up, it's
a glorious moment for all.
Bask.
They beat us, flopsy.
- It's generic kitty
litter from now on.
- [Crow meows]
The guns of navarone.
See you on the other
side, flopsy.
No way, I got eight more
lives, dickweed, meow.
Now what?
Ooh.
Oh, that rhubarb,
it's floating rhubarb?
[Screaming]
In the land of dairy queen,
we blow you up.
Ooh.
We're blowing up rhubarb.
A ball of fire.
Ooh, ooh, that all
the rhubarb, ooh.
Overbaked alaska.
[Laughs]
It's beautiful,
in some sick way.
[Groans]
Uh-oh.
Who am I?
Ernest hemingway,
get it.
No, no, no.
Hey, that's the
coward's way out.
♪ Now it's over ♪
♪ the man who shot himself ♪
♪♪
We now return to "ice station
zebra" already in progress.
Well, that's the end of q.
Good work, men.
It was a difficult
mission but we did it.
- Yes.
- Ooh.
I hope it wasn't too
tough on you.
It's been an honor
working with you, sir.
I love you, s--.
All right, let's go home.
Yes, sir.
It will take us about a half
hour to get home
and we're gonna film every
minute of it.
♪ This is the end
of the movie ♪
Mighty jack will be back in
robert ludlum's
the grim-jin flim-thin
prim-prim conspiracy.
Oh, wait, wait, we gotta see the
sandy frank side here.
Let's just stay quiet.
That's my favorite part.
You've seen
it a million times.
What a bother.
Just a moment.
♪ Sandy frank, sandy frank ♪
♪♪
[Gates closing]
[Accordion music playing]
[Robots chuckling as pirates]
Well, me clammy buckos,
the movie's over,
the pain is past and i's feel
like singing a plot shanty.
Be lively now,
me bonnie raitts.
♪ Oh slow
the plot down, laddie ♪
♪ slow the plot down ♪
♪ way hey slow the plot down ♪
♪ we'll scuttle the story
and run her aground ♪
♪ we'll try so hard
to slow the plot down ♪
Okay, now, who can tell me
their favorite scene from the
movie so far.
Tom, go ahead.
There was the, uh...
There was, uh...
Um, uh...
♪ Oh slow the plot down,
laddie ♪
♪ slow the plot down ♪
♪ way hey slow the plot down ♪
♪ with german italian
and japanese clowns ♪
♪ we'll try so hard
to slow the plot down ♪
Okay, well,
how about you, crow?
You must be full to bursting
with some fond memories
of today's movie,
come on, think hard.
Oh, uh... uh... um..
Uh, geez, joel,
I'm drawing a blank.
- Yeah, me too.
- I, um...
Oh, oh, I remember, uh, vaguely,
a guy locked--
locked in a room with another
guy and someone running.
♪ Oh make you a movie ♪
♪ that's long and a mess ♪
♪ way hey slow the plot down ♪
♪ just give us a script that
makes no friggin' sense ♪
♪ we'll try so hard
to slow the plot down ♪
Well, come on, you guys, I can
remember, I for one,
in vivid detail of frogmen
who, uh...
Just who-- who is mighty jack,
anyway?
Oh, wow, it just hit me,
I remember.
The scene where queequeg sits
motionless on the deck
meditating, foretelling the
death of the crew...
Oh, yeah, yeah, and scout sees
atticus shoot the mad dog
in the street and alex
goes and comes...
I remember, and then patrick
swayze walks in and says,
[all]
"It's my way
or the highway."
[Laughing like pirates]
- Come on, guys.
- Oh, my brain hurts.
Joel, I'm so confused.
It's really not that bad, you
guys, I for one actually feel
like I just got done listening
to two hours
of lou reed's
"metal machine music."
You know, my brain feels clean
as a whistle.
- And that's pretty good.
- Yeah, it is.
- Let's take it home.
- Okay.
♪ Oh slow the plot down laddies
slow the plot down ♪
♪ way hey slow the plot down ♪
♪ just scuttle the story
and run her aground ♪
♪ we'll try so hard
to slow the plot down ♪♪
[Talking like pirates]
My bonnie overlords,
what do you think?
Well, I think I'm going to
have to adjust
your air mixture again,
pirate dog.
It looks like it's getting
a little thin up there.
Push the button, frank.
Hard berg methought,
so cold, so vast,
with mortal damps
set overcast.
Exalting still thy
dankish breath,
adrift dissolving,
bound for death.
Isn't that right,
blind jim?
- [Snarling like a pirate]
- Oh, great, you've got
frank locked up,
he's quoting melville.
Go away.
Nor stir the slimy slug that
sprawls along...
Oh, shut up, frank.
♪♪